<news>

  <entry>
    <date>2026-02-06 12:00:00Z</date>
    <title>ZOMBIE-BACKEN</title>
    <title2>WAR3ZUK IN DEUTSCH</title2>
    <text>Dies ist eine vollständige deutsche Übersetzung der War3zuk AIO OverHaul Mod.
Alle Texte wurden originalgetreu und spielnah ins Deutsche übertragen,
ohne das Gameplay oder die Struktur der ursprünglichen Mod zu verändern.
Diese Übersetzung wird laufend gepflegt und an neue Mod-Versionen angepasst.
Hinweis: Es handelt sich ausschließlich um eine Übersetzung.
Alle Inhalte und Mechaniken stammen vom originalen Mod-Autor.
Solltet ihr noch was finden zum Übersetzten, dann kommt einfach in mein Discord.
Oder schaut auf Twitch vorbei. Würde mich über ein Follow sehr freuen.</text>
    <link>https://github.com/zimm794/War3zuk-AIO-OverHaul-GERMAN</link>
    <imagerelpath>war3zukZB.png</imagerelpath>
  </entry>


  <entry>
    <date>2025-08-27 12:00:00Z</date>
    <title>War3zuk</title>
    <title2>News</title2>
    <text>War3zuk AIO OverHaul 7D2D v2.5 B32 Final Stable Build

What this Mod is about, This Mod changes around 90% of the Total game Mechanics in the sense of Code, It adds many weapons All of which have been
bought from various stores to try to get the best looking and playing Mod I can manage, Its constantly being worked on and improved and should
always be kept upto date with the latest version of the main core game, The AIO also adds many Blocks and Different items that require abit
more learning in order to understand how it all works, A good example of this is the main weapons are no longer repaired using the default
repair kits but instead use 4 Custom made variants that are crafted on the player to do with each type of gun.. The link above explains the
Mod in much more detail.. Some of My Original Modlets that were used to create this AIO are as follows.. Around 20 or so more have been added
directly to the AIO that cant be made into Modlets due to them needing certain bits of code from the AIO so would cause Conflicts..
Thank you to the following Modlet creators who helped shape out the world with their modlets.</text>
    <link>https://dev.azure.com/war3zuk/_git/War3zuk-AIO-Mod-Launcher-v2?path=/ChangeLog.rtf</link>
    <imagerelpath>War3zukMenu.png</imagerelpath>
  </entry>

</news>